Collective Bargaining Agreements for New York State Employees 6124
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Collective Bargaining Agreements for New York State Employees
1942- 1948
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States. Department of Labor
Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS)
6124
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records.
5806205
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 30, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 23, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178/022 mf: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm
Collective bargaining -- New York (State); Labor unions -- New York (State); New York (State) -- Officials and employees; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics
5806205
- 1946 Agreements (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1947 Agreement (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Roll #1, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Roll #2, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Roll #3, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Roll #4, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Roll #5, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Roll #6, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Roll #7, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Rolls #8+#9, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Roll #10, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Rolls #11-12, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Roll #13, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Roll #14, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Roll #15, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Roll #16, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- "A" List of Agreements - Work Sheets, 1943-1945 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- "B" List of Agreements - Work Sheets, 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- "C" List of Agreements - Work Sheets, 1941-1945 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- "D" List of Agreements - Work Sheets, 1942-1945 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- "E" List of Agreements - work Sheets, 1941-1945 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- "F" List of Agreements - Work Sheets, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Microfilm Record, 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- "G" List of Agreements - Work Sheets, 1941-1945 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- "H" List of Contracts - Work Sheets, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- "J" List of Contracts - Work Sheet, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- "L" List of Contracts Work Sheets, 1941-1944 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- "M1 to M8" List of Agreements - Work Sheet, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- "M9 to M14" List of Contracts, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- "M15 to M19" List of Contracts, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- "M21A to M23" Lists of Contracts, 1942-1944 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- "N" List of Contracts, 1942-1944 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- "O" List of Contracts - Work Sheets, 1941-1945 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- "P" List of Contracts; some Work Sheets, 1941-1945 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- K, 1937-1945 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- "R" List of Contracts, 1943-1945 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- "S1 to S15" Lists of Contracts, 1943-1948 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- "S16 to S21" Lists of Contracts, 1941-1945 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- "T1 and T2" Lists of Contracts, 1941-1945 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- "T3 to T17" Lists of Contracts, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- "U" Lists of Contracts, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- "W" Lists of Contracts. Reel 228, 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- "FLU" Series. Reels 229-230-231 List of Contracts (Box 4, Folder 7)
- "LIU" Lines. Lists of Contracts Reels 239-240, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- "MU" List of Contracts (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Misc., 1942-1945 (Box 4, Folder 10)